Good morning.
It's been a while since we went out.
I'm glad.
I'm getting a lot of attention.
The season is a little different, but
we came to the sea.
Thank you for watching.
Please come back.
No!
What is today's project?
Today's project is...
Yes!
The first one is...
Intro-don with a spinning bat!
No!
The second one is...
Go!
Thank you for watching!
Please watch our next video!
Bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is the first one.
I've explained it a little roughly, but
there's a song called High Tension
Summer, right?
What is it?
Don't you know?
It's a nice song.
I thought that people who did something
like summer were more High Tension
Summer in the summer.
I think so.
Sometimes you say good things.
I think it was good to play TOHOKU's
High Tension Summer today.
Yeah!
I'm glad I came.
I've prepared three games.
I'll announce them one by one.
Please.
The first is GURUGURU BAD and Intro
Don.
Yes!
As the title says, we'll start with
TOHOKU's song.
It looks difficult.
Let's do our best!
You guys are liars!
The second is beach flag.
The last is a game of fishing.
The last is not related to the sea.
The third is a game of card game.
The last is a game of three-round.
The winner will be the final winner.
We will divide the teams.
I brought a nostalgic item.
What is it?
I prepared a lottery box.
When we cooked at the Cominping, we
divided into teams of animals.
Today, there are three penguins, pigs
and ducks in this box.
So this time, the people who draw the
same animal will compete rather than
teaming up.
I see.
Let's decide by having them draw the
same animal as last time.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
See you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
You're a cat.
What?
I'm a human.
Excuse me.
Yes.
She is a cat.
Excuse me.
Again?
She is cursed.
I'm going to go.
I'm going.
Thank you.
We've finished drawing.
Can you tell us who you are?
I'm Hachi.
I'm Buta.
We are Buta.
I'm Penguin.
I'm Akiru.
Let's divide into animals.
Let's do it.
First, let's do a roundabout.
You know the other side of the road
where you were running?
Run from there to this camera.
So, listen to the music over there,
turn the wheel 10 times, run, and put
the switch in front of the camera.
Please press it and answer.
Yes.
Let's do it.
Yeah!
Do your best!
We can do it!
Don't lose!
Do your best!
Please look at the camera.
Let's go!
The first challenge
The second challenge
Go! Go! Go!
Go for it!
She is going to win!
No way!
Go! Go!
Oh my god!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm so nervous!
You can do it!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to win!
This is fun!
This is more fun than a normal battle.
My legs are going to get eaten.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Natsumi.
Shinji, you don't know the song, do
you?
No.
You're too slow.
Good luck!
You're cool, Nari.
I'm going to do it.
You're cool.
Go!
Miao Tocci.
anding.
Shinji's turn.
Good luck!
You did good!
Kan철!
Woooo!
We are junior high school students.
How are you?
We are doing our best!
She is good!
She is laughing.
She is great!
Go for it!
She is not falling.
What is that?
Run!
You are not moving, right?
I am not moving.
She is a superstar!
What?
I'm so happy!
So, we are the three remaining.
Congratulations!
I've done my best so far.
That's enough.
You can run again.
I'm still tired.
What about the third runner?
Let's go back to the place before you
get tired.
Yes!
Let's go!
I'll do my best!
I'm nervous.
Is it going to start?
It looks like it.
Do your best!
Rinne, you're amazing!
Go, go, go!
Left, left.
Oh, run!
Oh, no!
Where did you go, Mo-chan?
Mo-chan disappeared!
She disappeared.
One point!
Youth High School Trip!
Mo-chan, good luck!
Good luck!
I didn't know.
Aehonmaki!
Good luck!
The battle is over.
It was fun.
It was really fun.
Hitomi won this battle.
It was cool.
Congratulations.
It was fun.
Please subscribe to my channel.
We are going to start the next game.
Please enjoy the game.
The next game is beach flag.
Yeah!
I think it's the first time to play
beach flag.
I think so, too.
The winner of the game will be decided
by 3 people.
Let's do our best!
I'm excited.
The animals are gone.
Let's divide the game into 3 people.
Good job!
OK.
The wolf howls.
That's amazing.
I'm old.
Well, then.
Oh, my God.
The wolf howls.
Let's start from the left, Yasumori,
Ritsuki, and Sakura.
The middle three and the right three
will play in order.
OK.
The winner of the game is Yasumori.
Yeah!
Let's go.
Ready.
Go.
It was a great effect.
I got it.
Let's do it!
Go for it!
You can do it!
Ready, go!
Go for it!
Which one?
Three?
The winner is...
Me!
Let's start!
Go for it!
Ready...
3...
Go for it!
The winner is Miya!
That's amazing!
You're going to get a high five, right?
Oh, no!
Go, Miya!
What are you doing?
What?
Wow!
You're a good match!
You should do it at a boys' school.
Wow!
I'm going to throw up.
It's decided.
Yasumori, Tachibana and Hitate.
It's a final round.
A single-color...
It's not a single-color party.
Version up?
We'll get ready for the final round.
The three finalists, please move to the
starting line.
We'll do our best.
We'll represent you.
I don't know.
To be continued.
Let's go for it!
Ready, go!
Go, go, go!
I'm a turtle!
Turtle!
Wakarin wins!
I'm a turtle!
Nice flag!
See you!
Thank you for watching.